

NIPUNI JAYASHANI

UI/UX Designer | Front - End Developer | Creative Graphic Designer

As a UI/UX Design professional with a background in business analysis and project management, I bring a unique skill set to create exceptional user experiences for digital products. With expertise in UI/UX design and engineering, I am well-versed in transforming complex concepts into intuitive and visually appealing interfaces.

Contact

| +94 71 414 65 80

| njayashani.1@gmail.com

in | https://www.linkedin.com/in/nipuni-jayashani

235/6/1 A,Temple Road, Pittugala,Malabe.

https://njayashani.github.io/

Professional Skills

Web Design	• • • • •
Design Active listening	• • • • •
Analytical Thinking	• • • • •
Problem Solving	• • • • •
Leadership	• • • • •
Pleasant speaking	• • • • •
Interpersonal skills	• • • • •
Applied psychology	• • • • •

Experience

UI/UX Engineer

FSD Codie

Jul 2023 - Present

UI/UX Designer

Adventa Holdings Pvt(Ltd)

Internship trainee
 Ceylon Electricity Board,

Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

Dec 2022 - Jun 2023

Education

University of Bedfordshire

BSc (Hons) in Computer Science and Software Engineering (2023-2024)

Esoft Metro campus

Pearson BTEC HND in Computing, Computer Software Engineering (2019-2022)

Lanka Professional Education Centre

Diploma in Human Resources Management (2019-2020)

Achievements

- Professional Certificate in Marketing (PCM) SLIM / Sep 2021
- Certificate in UI UX & Design Thinking / Jan 2022
- Associate Membership (ACPM) CPM Sri Lanka Sep 2022
- Certificate in UI/UX & Design Thinking (Beyond training Inst.)/Jan 2022
- Certificate in UI/UX Design (FSD Academy) /March 2023
- Provincial Art competition 2nd place Aug 2012

2023 - Present 2021-2022 2020 2019 **Tools** Figma Adobe XD

Adobe illustrator

Adobe photoshop

 $lackbox{0}$

Jira (project managment tool)

Project Experience

- TLMS
- Shopix
- CrowdLearn
- Innovation Management Platform
- Komoni Platform
- Inqtrix
- Efficore Platform
- Smart Kosher
- User interface design for "E-Music Cloud (EMC) online
- music platform" (Adobe XD)
- User Interface design for Travelling Site (Figma)
- User Interface design for Educational desktop application (Adobe XD)
- User Interface design for food mobile application (Adobe XD)

Programming Languages

JavaScript PHP C# HTML/CSS

Frameworks

React Bootstrap

Design software

Figma illustrator photoshop Jira

Languages

- English Professional Working Proficiency
- Sinhala Native or Bilingual Proficiency
- Tamil Limited working proficiency

Non - Related References

Mrs. Ruwani Wijesinghe

Ceylon Electricity Board (CEB) (Chief Engineer) Email:ruwanipj@gmail.com

Email: ruwanipj@gmail.com Contact No: +94 71 429 7679

Mr.W.M.N. Wijesena

Road Development Authority Udumulla Road, Baththramulla (Executive Engineer) Email: eecolombowp@gmail.com

Contact No: +94 112 884 388 /+94 772 009 730